Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Legal Department microfilmed entertainment contracts, 1924-1957 RL.11870
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
J. Walter Thompson Company. Legal Department microfilmed entertainment contracts
1924-1957
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
J. Walter Thompson Company
RL.11870
3.0 Linear Feet
Founded in 1864, the J. Walter Thompson Company (JWT) is one of the oldest and largest enduring advertising agencies in the United States. It is headquartered in New York. The JWT Legal Department microfilmed entertainment contracts include contracts for appearances on radio and television broadcasts; correspondence; folios (typically collections of documents relating to an actor's career, or casting for a broadcast program); letters of terms; notices of cancellations of contracts; photographs; talent releases and other printed documents. Talent featured in the sponsored programming include journalists, motion picture actors, musicians, politicians (such as Wendell Willkie), sports announcers, vaudeville blackface and dance performers, writers and other celebrities. Talent-based and variety shows drew from American and international performers, including African Americans and women. Sponsoring firms include Ballantine, Elgin, Ford, General Cigar, Kodak, Kraft, Lever Brothers, Lorillard, Nash Motors, Nestle, Owens-Illinois, RCA, Seven-Up, Shell, Standard Brands, Swift, Textron, Ward Baking and Wrigley. Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History.
Arrangement
Organized into the following series: Contracts for Broadcasting; Folios and Contracts; Letters of Terms--Accounts resigned; Radio Contracts.
Biographical / Historical
Founded in 1864, the J. Walter Thompson Company (JWT) is one of the oldest and largest enduring advertising agencies in the United States. It is headquartered in New York. Beginning in the 1930s, documents from several JWT departments and functions were microfilmed, including Legal Department, Treasurer's Office, As-Broadcast Scripts and Commercials for Radio and Television, Investigations, Publicity Department, Artwork, Consumer Panel, and Radio/Television Department. Documents were microfilmed in no order, and typed and hand-written indices were produced for the microfilms. The present electronic collection guide is based largely on transcriptions of the paper indices produced by the JWT Information Center library staff. It is believed that once microfilmed, most of the original documents were destroyed.
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Provenance
The J. Walter Thompson Company. Legal Department microfilmed entertainment contracts were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift in 1986.
Related Materials
Related materials may be found in the following Hartman Center collections:
J. Walter Thompson Company. 16mm microfilmed Legal Department records
J. Walter Thompson Company. Account files
J. Walter Thompson Company. Legal Department records
J. Walter Thompson Company. Legal Department microfilmed talent consents and releases
J. Walter Thompson Company. Radio/Television Department records.
Scope and Contents
The JWT Legal Department microfilmed entertainment contracts include contracts for appearances on radio and television broadcasts; correspondence; folios (typically collections of documents relating to an actor's career, or casting for a broadcast program); letters of terms; notices of cancellations of contracts; photographs; talent releases and other printed documents. Talent featured in the sponsored programming include journalists, motion picture actors, musicians, politicians (such as Wendell Willkie), sports announcers, vaudeville blackface and dance performers, writers and other celebrities. Talent-based and variety shows drew from American and international performers, including African Americans and women. Sponsoring firms include Ballantine, Elgin, Ford, General Cigar, Kodak, Kraft, Lever Brothers, Lorillard, Nash Motors, Nestle, Owens-Illinois, RCA, Seven-Up, Shell, Standard Brands, Swift, Textron, Ward Baking and Wrigley.
Advertising agencies -- United States -- History; Radio broadcasting -- United States; Television broadcasting -- United States -- History; Radio advertising -- United States -- History; Television advertising -- United States -- History; John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History; Ward Baking Company; Textron, Inc.; Standard Brands Incorporated; Seven-Up Company; Radio Corporation of America; P. Lorillard Company; P. Ballantine & Sons; Lever Brothers Company; Kraft Foods Company; General Cigar Company (Philadelphia, Pa.); Ford Motor Company; Eastman Kodak Company; Wm. Wrigley Jr. Company; Swift & Company; Shell Oil Company; Nestlé; Nash Motors Company; Willkie, Wendell L. (Wendell Lewis), 1892-1944
- Contracts for Broadcasting, 1929-1949; undated; 1
  - American Tobacco Company, 1934; 1
    - Contracts, 1934 (Film-reel 83)
  - Andrew Jergens, 1931-1936; 2
    - Cornelia Otis Skinner, 1935 June 2-Aug. 25 (Film-reel 83)
    - Elliott Jacoby, 1935 June 2-Aug. 25 (Film-reel 83)
    - Lucien Schmidt, 1932-1936 (Film-reel 83)
    - Ray Perkins, 1931 Sept. 2-1932 June 30 (Film-reel 83)
    - Walter Winchell, 1932-1936 (Film-reel 83)
    - William Scholtz, 1932 Dec. 4-1933 May 23 (Film-reel 83)
  - Atlantis Sales, 1943; 3
    - John Wayne--Release, 1943 (Film-reel 151)
  - B.F. Goodrich, 1930-1931; 4
    - Arthur Allen, 1930 Dec. 242-1931 Mar. 21 (Film-reel 83)
    - Arthur Allen and Phillips Lord, 1930 Sept. 24-Dec. 20 (Film-reel 83)
    - Phillips Lord, 1930 June 23-Dec. 20 (Film-reel 83)
  - Calsodent, 1930-1940; 5
    - Bob Howard, 1939 Oct. 19-1940 Apr. 16 (Film-reel 83)
    - Frank Luther, 1934 Apr. 27-July 20 (Film-reel 83)
    - Marley Sherris, 1930 Apr. 1-1934 Sept. 28 (Film-reel 83)
  - Cream of Wheat, 1929-1936; 6
    - Alexander Woollcott, 1934-1936 (Film-reel 83)
    - Angelo Patri correspondence (no contract), 1930s (Film-reel 83)
    - Buck Rogers folios, 1935-1936 (Film-reel 83)
    - E.R. Johnstone, 1935 Dec. 20-1936 May 22 (Film-reel 83)
    - John F. Dille Co. (Buck Rogers), 1935-1936 (Film-reel 83)
    - Leggett Brown, 1935 Oct. 6-Dec. 29 (Film-reel 83)
    - Peg La Centra, 1934 Dec. 16 (Film-reel 83)
      Scope and Contents
      Stage name of singer Margherita Maria Francesca LaCentra (1910-1996); also performed under the name Barbara Fulton
    - Ray Heatherton, 1935 Oct. 20 (Film-reel 83)
    - William Steinke and Muriel Harbator with orchestra, 1929-1933 (Film-reel 83)
  - Davey Tree Company, 1930-1932; 7
    - Alma Ritchell, 1930 May 11 (Film-reel 83)
    - Harold Branch and Richard Maxwell, 1930 June 1 (Film-reel 83)
    - Kurtis Brownell, 1932 Jan. 24-Apr. 17 (Film-reel 83)
    - Mr. Goldwaithe and Orchestra, 1930-1932 (Film-reel 83)
    - Norman Horn, 1932 Jan. 24-Apr. 17 (Film-reel 83)
    - Paul Parks, 1930-1931 (Film-reel 83)
    - Sam Herman, 1930 Dec. 14 (Film-reel 83)
    - Steele Jamison, 1930 June 1 (Film-reel 83)
  - Eastman Kodak, 1930-1940; 8
    - Alois Havrilla, 1931 Mar. 27-Sept. 11 (Film-reel 83)
    - Angelo Patri, 1934 Apr. 17-May 15 (Film-reel 83)
    - Artella Dickson, 1932 June 3 (Film-reel 83)
    - Bobwin Russian Imperial Balalaika Orchestra, 1932 Aug. 12 (Film-reel 83)
    - Borrah Minnevitch, 1932 Sept. 2 (Film-reel 83)
    - Bradford Browne, 1930 Apr. 10-July 24 (Film-reel 83)
    - Cornelia Otis Skinner, 1932 Sept. 9 (Film-reel 83)
    - Countess Olga Medolago Albani, 1930-1931 (Film-reel 83)
    - Dixie Jubilee Singers, 1932 July 22 (Film-reel 83)
    - Dr. Howard W. Haggard, 1931-1932 (Film-reel 83)
    - Ed Clark, 1939 Jan. 27 (Film-reel 83)
    - Imogene Coca, 1940 Feb. 9 (Film-reel 83)
    - Jack Parker, Frank Luther, Philip Dewey, James Stanley, Will Donaldson, 1930-1931 (Film-reel 83)
    - Joan Edwards, 1938 Jan. 21 (Film-reel 83)
    - John Mulholland, 1940 Feb. 9 (Film-reel 83)
    - Madame Zenida Nicolina and her guitar accompanist, 1932 June 17 (Film-reel 83)
    - Nancy Noland Noel, 1939 Jan. 27 (Film-reel 83)
    - Nate Leipsig, 1938 Jan. 21 (Film-reel 83)
    - Nathaniel Shilkret, 1931-1932 (Film-reel 83)
    - Nick Lucas, 1932 Aug. 26 (Film-reel 83)
    - Norton Cotterill, 1934 Apr. 25-May 6 (Film-reel 83)
    - Oswald Garrison Villard, 1940 Feb. 22 (Film-reel 83)
    - Paul Robeson, 1932 (Film-reel 83)
    - Prince Mendez, 1939 Jan. 27 (Film-reel 83)
    - Ray Knight, 1938 Jan. 21 (Film-reel 83)
    - Roy Smeck, 1932 Aug. 12 (Film-reel 83)
    - Salzado Harp Ensemble, 1932 May 13 (Film-reel 83)
    - Thelma Kessler, 1932 Apr. 29-Sept. 9 (Film-reel 83)
    - Will Donaldson, 1932 Apr. 29-Sept. 9 (Film-reel 83)
  - Elgin National Watch, 1935-1936; 1947; 9
    - C.A. Wynn, 1936 Nov. 7 (Film-reel 83)
    - Ed Thorgensen, 1936 Oct. 3-Dec. 26 (Film-reel 83)
    - Elmer Layden, 1936 Nov. 14 (Film-reel 83)
    - Gar Davidson, 1936 Oct. 10 (Film-reel 83)
    - H.J. Mehre, 1936 Nov. 21 (Film-reel 83)
    - James H. Crowley, 1936 Oct. 31 (Film-reel 83)
    - Kay Kyser, 1936 Oct. 3-Dec. 26 (Film-reel 83)
    - Lou Little, 1936 Nov. 28 (Film-reel 83)
    - Matty Ball, 1936 Oct. 10 (Film-reel 83)
    - Maurie Lipsey, 1936 Mar. 17-June 9 (Film-reel 83)
    - Mills Brothers, 1935 Oct. 4-Dec. 27 (Film-reel 83)
    - Paul Gallico, 1936 Dec. 19 (Film-reel 83)
    - Ray Flaherty, 1936 Dec. 12 (Film-reel 83)
    - Slip Madigan, 1936 Oct. 24 (Film-reel 83)
    - Television folios, 1947 (Film-reel 442)
  - Emerson Drug, 1935-1938; 10
    - Donald Dickson, 1938 Apr. 3-June 26 (Film-reel 83)
    - Eddie Garr, 1938 Jan. 12-26 (Film-reel 83)
    - F. Chase Taylor, 1938 Apr. 3-June 26 (Film-reel 83)
    - Folios, 1935-1936; 1938 (Film-reel 83)
    - Harriet Parsons, 1938 Jan. 19-June 29 (Film-reel 83)
    - International Casino, 1938 Jan. 12 (Film-reel 83)
    - Nils T. Granlund, 1935 July 9-1936 Jan. 21 (Film-reel 83)
    - Pathe News, 1935 Apr. 8-July 6 (Film-reel 83)
    - Sidney Skolsky, 1937 Oct. 6-Dec. 29 (Film-reel 83)
    - The Stork Club, 1938 Jan. 19 (Film-reel 83)
    - Tito Guizar, 1936 Feb. 3-May 1 (Film-reel 83)
    - Tom Howard and George Shelton, 1935 Oct. 8-1936 Jan. 21 (Film-reel 83)
  - Ford Motor Company, 1947; 11
    - Television folios, 1947 (Film-reel 442)
  - General Cigar, 1932-1936; 12
    - Buccaneers Octette, 1935 Apr. 17-Sept. 25 (Film-reel 83)
    - Burns & Allen, 1932-1935 (Film-reel 83)
    - Ferde Grofe, 1935 Apr. 17-Sept. 25 (Film-reel 83)
    - Folios, 1935 Jan. -Sept. (Film-reel 83)
    - Folios, 1939 Sept. 30-1942 Sept. 19 (Film-reel 152)
    - Guy Lombardo and His Royal Canadians, 1933-1934 (Film-reel 83)
    - Harms Inc. for Herbert Spencer, 1934 Oct. 17-1935 May 13 (Film-reel 83)
    - Lou Little, 1936 Oct. 2-Dec. 4 (Film-reel 83)
    - Phil Ragan, 1932 Sept. 21-1933 Apr. 13 (Film-reel 83)
    - Raymond Gram Swing, 1939 Sept. 25-1942 Sept. 23 (Film-reel 152)
    - Robert E. Dolan, 1934 Sept. 19-1935 May 13 (Film-reel 83)
    - Santos Ortega, 1932 Mar. 7-Sept. 14 (Film-reel 83)
    - William Brenton, 1933 Mar. 22-May 24 (Film-reel 83)
  - General Electric--Television, 1940; 13
    - Permissions, 1940 (Film-reel 405)
  - Gruen Watch Makers Guild, 1930-1931; 14
    - Alexander Woollcott, 1930Sept. 15-Dec. 12 (Film-reel 83)
    - Earl Gilbert, 1931 Mar. 5-Dec. 19 (Film-reel 83)
    - Tom Neely, 1931 Sept. 5-Dec. 19 (Film-reel 83)
  - Horlicks Ltd., 1938-1939; 15
    - One Special for Doc--Consent, 1938-1939 (Film-reel 151)
      Note: Broadcasts to be given over Luxembourg, Normandy, Paris
    - When the Sun Rises--Consent, 1939 May 9 (Film-reel 151)
  - J. Kitchen & Sons, 1941; 16
    - Correspondence for Australian Broadcasting, 1941 (Film-reel 151)
  - J.B. Williams, 1936-1943; 17
    - A.B. McGinley, 1936 Apr. 13 (Film-reel 151)
    - Al Robinson, 1938 July (Film-reel 151)
    - Arnold Johnson, 1943 Apr. 9 (Film-reel 151)
    - Bob Howard, 1938 Apr. 17-1939 Oct. 18 (Film-reel 151)
    - Circus, Saints and Sinners, 1943 May (Film-reel 151)
    - Dr. Harry Strandhagen (True and False), 1937 Oct. 7-1943 Oct. 1 (Film-reel 151)
      Shell Oil contract (reel 137) cancelled; went to Williams 1937 Dec. 10
    - Drew Pearson, Bob Allen, 1940 June-July (Film-reel 151)
    - George Hicks, 1939 Feb. 15-Oct. 12 (Film-reel 151)
    - Gliding Swing program folios, 1938-1940 (Film-reel 151)
    - Himan Brown--Adventures of Nero Wolfe, 1943 Mar. 31-Oct. 3 (Film-reel 151)
    - Jack Dempsey, 1936 Apr. 28 (Film-reel 151)
    - Lewis Charles, 1938 Apr. 18 (Film-reel 151)
    - Mutual Broadcasting System Acceptance by Radio Mirror, 1938 Mar. (Film-reel 151)
    - Neal O'Hara, 1936 July 27 (Film-reel 151)
    - Ted Steele (G. Thorton Steil), 1940 Jan. 15-July 12 (Film-reel 151)
    - Tex O'Rourke, 1943 May 26-June (Film-reel 151)
    - True and False program folios, 1937-1943 (Film-reel 151)
    - Washington Merry-Go-Round folios, 1940 July-Sept. (Film-reel 151)
    - William Spargrove, 1939 Feb. 13-1940 July 8 (Film-reel 151)
    - WOR Electrical Transcription Recording Service, 1938 Jan. 27 (Film-reel 151)
  - Johns-Manville, 1933-1938; 18
    - Edwin C. Hill, 1936 Jan. 13 (Film-reel 83)
    - Edwin Franko Goldman, 1936 Jan. 13 (Film-reel 83)
    - Floyd Gibbons, 1933-1935 (Film-reel 83)
    - Folios, 1935-1936 (Film-reel 83)
    - Gabriel Heatter, 1938 Feb. 1-Dec. 31 (Film-reel 83)
    - Graham McNamee, 1936 Jan. 13 (Film-reel 83)
    - Kate Smith, 1936 Jan. 13 (Film-reel 83)
    - Merrill Dennison, 1937 Mar. 4 (Film-reel 83)
    - Myles Lesker, 1934 May 12 (Film-reel 83)
    - Nathaniel Shilkret, 1934 May 12 (Film-reel 83)
    - Tom Howard and George Shelton, 1936 Jan. 13 (Film-reel 83)
    - Victor Young, 1933 Sept. 25 (Film-reel 83)
  - Kellogg, 1939-1941; 19
    - Adventure of the Understanding Men--Consent, 1939 Mar. 3 (Film-reel 151)
    - Allan Jones, 1939 Mar. 5 (Film-reel 151)
    - Basil Rathbone, 1939 (Film-reel 151)
    - Boris Karloff, 1939 Apr. 16 (Film-reel 151)
    - C.G. and Kathleen Norris, 1939 Apr. 9 (Film-reel 151)
    - Deems Taylor, 1939 May 28 (Film-reel 151)
    - Donald Woods, 1939 Feb. 19 (Film-reel 151)
    - Dr. Hackenbush--Consent, 1939 Apr. 16 (Film-reel 151)
    - Frank Lloyd Wright, 1939 June 25 (Film-reel 151)
    - Gene Mako, 1939 Apr. 23 (Film-reel 151)
    - Groucho Marx for use of Olive--Consent, 1941 Feb. 8 (Film-reel 151)
    - In the Fog--Consent, 1939 Jan. 20 (Film-reel 151)
    - Invitation to the Dance--Consent, 1939 Feb. 1 (Film-reel 151)
    - Irvin S. Cobb, 1939 May 14 (Film-reel 151)
    - James Hilton, 1939 July 2 (Film-reel 151)
    - John Carter, 1939 Mar. 19 (Film-reel 151)
    - John Erskine, 1939 July 2 (Film-reel 151)
    - John Gunther, 1939 Feb. 19 (Film-reel 151)
    - John McClain, 1939 May 7 (Film-reel 151)
    - Jose Iturbi, 1939 (Film-reel 151)
    - Kay Francis, 1939 Feb. 26 (Film-reel 151)
    - Louis Bromfield, 1939 June 18 (Film-reel 151)
    - Madeleine Carroll, 1939 Mar. 12; May 7 (Film-reel 151)
    - Marc Connelly, 1939 June 11 (Film-reel 151)
    - Marian Anderson, 1939 Feb. 12; Mar. 12 (Film-reel 151)
    - Materials from Arthur Sheekman--Consent, 1939 Feb. 5 (Film-reel 151)
    - Maureen O'Sullivan, 1939 Mar. 26 (Film-reel 151)
    - Merle Oberon, 1939 Mar. 19 (Film-reel 151)
    - Moroni Olsen, 1939 Feb. 19 (Film-reel 151)
    - Mr. Chips and Young Waveny--Consent, 1939 June 30 (Film-reel 151)
    - Nina Martini, 1939 Apr. 23 (Film-reel 151)
    - Ogden Nash, 1939 Mar. 19 (Film-reel 151)
    - Robert Cummings, 1939 Apr. 9 (Film-reel 151)
    - Rose Bampton, 1939 Feb. 26; Mar. 5 (Film-reel 151)
    - The Other Curb--Consent, 1939 Apr. 8 (Film-reel 151)
    - Unlit Room--Consent, 1939 Feb. 23 (Film-reel 151)
    - Vilhjamur Stefansson, 1939 June 4 (Film-reel 151)
    - Walter Connolly, 1939 Mar. 5 (Film-reel 151)
    - Wuthering Heights--Consent, 1939 Mar. 19 (Film-reel 151)
  - Kellogg--Australia and New Zealand, undated; 20
    - Contracts and extensions, undated (Film-reel 151)
  - Kellogg--Howie Wing, 1933-1939; 21
    - Folios, 1938 Oct.-1939 June (Film-reel 83)
    - Mary Parker, 1938 Oct. 1-Dec. 31 (Film-reel 83)
    - Neil O'Malley, 1938 Oct. 1-1939 June 30 (Film-reel 83)
    - Ralph Edwards, 1939 Feb. 13-June 30 (Film-reel 83)
    - Robert Strauss, 1938 Nov. 21-1939 June 30 (Film-reel 83)
    - Wilfred G. Moore, 1938 Oct. 3-1939 June 30 (Film-reel 83)
    - William Janney, 1938-1939 (Film-reel 83)
    - World Broadcasting System and N.W. Ayer, 1930Sept. 15-Dec. 12 (Film-reel 83)
  - Kellogg--The Circle, 1938-1939; 22
    - Basil Rathbone, 1939 Feb. 16 (Film-reel 83)
    - Carole Lombard, 1939 Jan. 15-Feb. 5 (Film-reel 83)
    - Cary Grant, 1939 Jan. 15-Feb. 19 (Film-reel 83)
    - Colonel Stoopnagle (F. Chase Taylor), 1938 Dec. 15-1939 Jan. 15 (Film-reel 83)
    - Folios, 1939 Jan.-July (Film-reel 83)
    - Groucho and Chico Marx, 1939 Jan. 15-July 15 (Film-reel 83)
    - John Whedon, 1939 Jan. 1-July 15 (Film-reel 83)
    - Lawrence Tibbett, 1939 Jan. 15-July 15 (Film-reel 83)
    - Madeleine Carroll, 1939 Apr. 2-June 4 (Film-reel 83)
    - Owen Davis Jr., 1939 Apr. 30-July 9 (Film-reel 83)
    - Robert E. Dolan, 1939 Jan. 15-July 9 (Film-reel 83)
    - Ronald Colman, 1939 Jan. 15-Feb. 5 (Film-reel 83)
    - The Foursome, 1939 Jan. 15-July 15 (Film-reel 83)
  - Kops Brothers, 1931-1935; 23
    - Basil Ruysdael, 1934 Nov. 13-1935 Feb. 5 (Film-reel 83)
    - Frank Curran, 1934 Nov. 13-1935 Feb. 5 (Film-reel 83)
    - Harry Stockwell, 1934 Nov. 13-1935 Feb. 5 (Film-reel 83)
    - Marion Carter, 1931 Mar. 30-June 26 (Film-reel 83)
  - Kraft Cheese, 1933-1940; 24
    - Al Jolson, 1933 June 26-1934 July 26 (Film-reel 68)
    - Bing Crosby, 1935 Dec. 5-26 (Film-reel 83)
    - Deems Taylor, 1933 June 26-1934 July 12 (Film-reel 68)
    - Dorothy English, 1939 (Film-reel 68)
    - Ford Bond, 1934-1935 (Film-reel 83)
    - Helen Jepson, 1934 May 17-1935 Nov. 7 (Film-reel 83)
    - Howard Clancy, 1935 July 9-25 (Film-reel 68)
    - Jimmy Dorsey and orchestra, 1936-1937 July 1 (Film-reel 68)
    - Folios, 1938-1940 (Film-reel 68)
    - Lou Holtz, 1935 Mar. 7-July 11 (Film-reel 68)
    - Miscellaneous, 1934-1937 (Film-reel 68)
    - Mr. Balieff, 1934 Apr. 26-May 17 (Film-reel 68)
    - Norman Cordon, 1934 May 3-Aug. 30 (Film-reel 68)
    - Nuchem (Nahum) Stutchkoff, 1938 Mar. 13-Sept. 4 (Film-reel 68)
    - Oscar Goren, 1938 Mar. 13-Sept. 4 (Film-reel 68)
    - Pat Friday, 1939 June 15-Sept. 28 (Film-reel 68)
    - Paul Whiteman, 1933-1935 (Film-reel 83)
    - Ramona Davies, 1935 (Film-reel 83)
    - Sidney Gordon, 1938 Mar. 13-Sept. 4 (Film-reel 68)
    - The Foursome, 1938 July 1-Oct. 13 (Film-reel 68)
    - The King's Men, 1935 June 3-Dec. 26 (Film-reel 83)
  - Kraft Music Hall--Shell Chateau, 1936; 25
    - Harriet Hilliard, 1936 July 3 (Film-reel 160)
  - Kraft Television Theatre, 1947; 26
    - A Doll's House--Rights, 1947 June 18 (Film-reel 442)
    - Adele Longmire, 1947 Nov. 5; 26 (Film-reel 442)
    - Aime Gauvin, 1947 Sept. 10; Nov. 26 (Film-reel 442)
    - Alexander Clarke, 1947 (Film-reel 442)
    - Alice Yourman, 1947 June 25 (Film-reel 442)
    - Allan Stevenson, 1947 Dec. 31 (Film-reel 442)
    - Andree Wallace, 1947 (Film-reel 442)
    - Ann Sargeant, 1947 July 2 (Film-reel 442)
    - Anna Russell, 1947 Dec. 10 (Film-reel 442)
    - Arthur Franz, 1947 (Film-reel 442)
    - Audrey Binham, 1947 Sept. 3 (Film-reel 442)
    - Barbara Joyce, 1947 May 14 (Film-reel 442)
    - Barry Doig, 1947 July 30 (Film-reel 442)
    - Ben Lackland, 1947 Aug. 6; 13 (Film-reel 442)
    - Bernard Grant, 1947 July 9 (Film-reel 442)
    - Bernard Randall, 1947 Aug. 20 (Film-reel 442)
    - Berni Gould, 1947 May 14 (Film-reel 442)
    - Betty Buchler, 1947 June 25 (Film-reel 442)
    - Bill Griffis, 1947 Oct. 1; 8 (Film-reel 442)
    - Blanchard McKee, 1947 May 14 (Film-reel 442)
    - Blind Alley--Rights, 1947 Oct. 29 (Film-reel 442)
    - Bob Lied, 1947 Aug. 13 (Film-reel 442)
    - But Not Goodbye, 1947 Nov. 19 (Film-reel 442)
    - Byron Russell, 1947 Oct. 22; Dec. 24 (Film-reel 442)
    - Cathleen Cordell, 1947 July 30; Sept. 17 (Film-reel 442)
    - Charity Grace, 1947 June 11; Nov. 19 (Film-reel 442)
    - Charles Francis, 1947 May 7 (Film-reel 442)
    - Charles Nevil, 1947 Dec. 31 (Film-reel 442)
    - Cherry Hardy, 1947 Aug. 13 (Film-reel 442)
    - Claude Horton, 1947 Oct. 22 (Film-reel 442)
    - Consider Lily--Rights, 1947 July 16 (Film-reel 442)
    - Cora Smith, 1947 (Film-reel 442)
    - Craig's Wife--Rights, 1947 Sept. 10 (Film-reel 442)
    - Cynthia Lathum, 1947 Sept. 24 (Film-reel 442)
    - David Frank, 1947 Dec. 24 (Film-reel 442)
    - Don Keefer, 1947 (Film-reel 442)
    - Dorrit Kelton, 1947 (Film-reel 442)
    - Double Door--Rights, 1947 May 7 (Film-reel 442)
    - Douglas Parkhirst, 1947 May 21 (Film-reel 442)
    - Drew Conklin, 1947 Dec. 24 (Film-reel 442)
    - Earl Gilbert, 1947 Aug. 20 (Film-reel 442)
    - Earl Hammond, 1947 Nov. 12 (Film-reel 442)
    - Ed Reichert, 1947 Dec. 3 (Film-reel 442)
    - Eda Heinemann, 1947 Nov. 12 (Film-reel 442)
    - Eddie Mayehoff, 1947 May 14 (Film-reel 442)
    - Eileen Heckart, 1947 (Film-reel 442)
    - Eleanor Wilson, 1947 May 7; 28 (Film-reel 442)
    - Elizabeth Eustis, 1947 Nov. 12 (Film-reel 442)
    - Elizabeth Morgan, 1947 May 21; July 23 (Film-reel 442)
    - Elliott Reid, 1947 Dec. 10 (Film-reel 442)
    - Ernest Graves, 1947 Sept. 3 (Film-reel 442)
    - Estelle Dodge, 1947 June 4 (Film-reel 442)
    - Eva Marie Saint, 1947 Dec. 3 (Film-reel 442)
    - Everett Gammon, 1947 May 21 (Film-reel 442)
    - Flora Campbell, 1947 (Film-reel 442)
    - Folios and some rights, 1947 May 7 (Film-reel 442)
    - Frances Charles, 1947 May 14 (Film-reel 442)
    - Francis De Sales, 1947 June 18 (Film-reel 442)
    - Frank Thomas Sr., 1947 Oct. 22 (Film-reel 442)
    - Frederick de Wilde, 1947 July 9; Aug. 6 (Film-reel 442)
    - Gene O'Donnell, 1947 Dec. 3 (Film-reel 442)
    - George Mitchell, 1947 May 7; June 4 (Film-reel 442)
    - George Petrie, 1947 May 28 (Film-reel 442)
    - Gordon Mills, 1947 Oct. 29 (Film-reel 442)
    - Gordon Peters, 1947 Dec. 3 (Film-reel 442)
    - Grace Reddy, 1947 Sept. 10; Dec. 31 (Film-reel 442)
    - Grant Calhoun, 1947 Nov. 5; 26 (Film-reel 442)
    - Guy Spaull, 1947 Sept. 17; Dec. 10 (Film-reel 442)
    - Helen Parrish, 1947 Aug. 20 (Film-reel 442)
    - Hildy Parks, 1947 (Film-reel 442)
    - Holiday--Rights, 1947 Dec. 17 (Film-reel 442)
    - Hugh Reilly, 1947 Nov. 19; Dec. 17 (Film-reel 442)
    - Humphrey Davis, 1947 Oct. 1 (Film-reel 442)
    - I Like It Here--Rights, 1947 June 25 (Film-reel 442)
    - Inge Adams, 1947 (Film-reel 442)
    - Interference--Rights, 1947 July 30 (Film-reel 442)
    - Isham Constable, 1947 Aug. 27; Sept. 3 (Film-reel 442)
    - J.W. Austin, 1947 Sept. 24 (Film-reel 442)
    - Jack Manning, 1947 Aug. 20 (Film-reel 442)
    - Jack Orrison, 1947 Dec. 3; 24 (Film-reel 442)
    - Jackie Diamond, 1947 Dec. 24 (Film-reel 442)
    - Jane Bennett Hix, 1947 Aug. 20; Dec. 31 (Film-reel 442)
    - January Thaw--Rights, 1947 Oct. 8 (Film-reel 442)
    - Jay Jackson, 1947 May 14 (Film-reel 442)
    - Jay Meredith, 1947 July 9 (Film-reel 442)
    - Jean Cameron, 1947 Nov. 12 (Film-reel 442)
    - Jim Boles, 1947 Dec. 24 (Film-reel 442)
    - Joan Copeland, 1947 June 11; July 16 (Film-reel 442)
    - Joann Dolan, 1947 Sept. 10; Oct. 29 (Film-reel 442)
    - John Baragrey, 1947 May 7; Oct. 15 (Film-reel 442)
    - John Conway, 1947 July 9; 16 (Film-reel 442)
    - John Morley, 1947 Aug. 6; Oct. 8 (Film-reel 442)
    - John Seymour, 1947 (Film-reel 442)
    - John Shellie, 1947 Nov. 19 (Film-reel 442)
    - John Stanley, 1947 May 21; Aug. 6 (Film-reel 442)
    - John Stephen, 1947 (Film-reel 442)
    - Jon Richards, 1947 May 7 (Film-reel 442)
    - Joseph Boley, 1947 May 7; June 18 (Film-reel 442)
    - Katherine Hall, 1947 Aug. 20 (Film-reel 442)